Our new Speaker of the House, Mike Johnson, is a Dominionist.
Look up Dominionism and the Seven Mountain Mandate,
and let's look really quickly.
Our democracy right now is teetering.
It's slowly eroding.
And let's look at the difference between an authoritarian theocracy
and what we have now that is fleeting, which is our democracy,
because they're very different.
And listen, Mike Johnson is two steps away from the presidency.
Okay?
Pay attention.
All right.
In an authoritarian theocracy, obedience is very important
versus in a democracy, freedom.
Over here, religious authority.
They tell us what to do and how to worship.
In a democracy, religious freedom.
Worship however you want or not at all.
Here, they suppress political dissent.
Over here, encouraging freedom of speech.
Under an authoritarian theocracy, criticism equals blasphemy, equals punishment.
Whereas in a democracy, criticism is allowed and encouraged.
It's how we get things done.
It's how we hash out ideas.
Over here, you have state-run media.
Whereas over here, you have journalism, the free press.
Finally, well, not finally.
This is just that there's so much more to it.
The chosen are in charge.
Dominionists and Mike Johnson and his ilk believe that they were chosen by God to run this country
and that America needs to be a Christian nation.
In a democracy, we believe in equality.
That anyone, given hard work and good ideas, could run for president.
Or could serve the people.
It's a democracy.
The people are in charge.
Over here, a small group of religious leaders is in charge.
And it's autocratic.
Now listen, our democracy is far from perfect.
It is messy.
It's messy, messy.
But I'll take this mess any day over the alternative.
It's really important that we vote and pay attention to what's going on.
Shine a light on it.
Alright, thanks.